Hello?
Dean, 你准备好了吗?
Dean,are you ready?
我马上就下来.
I'll be right down.
不用担心. 我们有足够的时间.
Don't worry.We have plenty of time.
嗨!
Hi.
去纽约的火车不会离开 直到1:30左右.
The train to New York doesn't leave till 1:30 or so.
我们看看.
Let's see.
你的意思是1:25这趟?
Do you mean the 1:25?
Yeah, 就是这个.
Yeah,that's it.
Kevin, 那是趟慢车. 看?
Kevin,that's a local.See?
它是用蓝色标记的.
It's in blue.
它到处停.
It stops everywhere.
它到纽约 在今晚的7:39!
It arrives in New York at 7:39 tonight!
Well, 我们不想要那个.
Well,we don't want that.
有快车吗?
Is there an express?
我看到了. 它们是红色的.
I see.They're in red.
下一趟1:10离开. Damn!
The next one leaves at 1:10. Damn!
-那趟车之后的下一趟什么时候呢? -4:15
-When's the next train after that? -4:15.
它不在那儿.
It's not there.
1:10开的那趟?
The 1:10?
它有一个标记在它旁边. 一个正方形.
It's got a symbol beside it.A square.
那是什么意思?
What does that mean?
这趟火车周末不开.
This train does not run on weekends.